Alright.
Board of selectmen is coming out of executive
session at 09:41.
I'm gonna make a motion to,
increase
all
nonunion
town employee,
pay rates by 4%
with the following exceptions.
We want to increase the
child,
children's librarian rate to $19.32,
And we would like to increase
the,
rate for
the senior
busing transportation,
employee, Ellie Scoo, to $20.94.
Is that it, Jeff? That's it. That's it on the the rates,
and we just have another motion that we're gonna make after this. I'll second that then, Jeff.
Okay. Further discussion on any of those items?
All those in favor, aye.
Aye.
Alright.
And then I
would like to make a motion that
in this current fiscal year
that
we
provide a performance
bonus to
to mister Bell, the town custodian of $1,500
for the excellent work that he is
he has done and is currently doing
related to the upkeep of the town hall.
I'll second.
Alright. Further discussion on that item?
All those in favor, aye. Aye. Aye.
Okay.
I think that's it for tonight. So we have till next Monday. And then Eric, you will sit there and as we have requested, provide
updated budget summary, and then we can sit there and review it and final next week before
we pass it on to the Board Finance.
Okay.
Anybody?
Motion to adjourn.
Second.
Okay. All all in favor. Aye.
Aye. Thank you very much.
Good night. Good night.